// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "By the time they found him, he .................................",
    answer: "had died",
    options: [ "died", "had died","have died","has die" ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "He ..................................... many years ago.",
    answer: "died",
    options: ["died","had died","has died","was dying"]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question:"By that time, everybody .................. asleep.",
    answer: "was",
    options: [
      "had been", "was","shall","will being" ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "She told me that something ........................................ to him.",
    answer: "had happened",
    options: ["happened","had happened","have happened","has happened" ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "I ............................................ about it until you mentioned it.",
    answer: "hadn't thought",
    options: [ "didn't think", "hadn't thought","haven't thought","hasn't thought" ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: " She ............................................. him at once.",
    answer: "recognized",
    options: ["has recognized", "recognized","had recognized","have recognized"  ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: " I ....................................... him yesterday.",
    answer: "saw",
    options: [ "saw", "have seen","had seen","has seen" ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question:"He ......................................... in 1960.",
    answer: "was born",
    options: [ "born", "had born","was born","has born" ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: " I ............................................... enough time to finish the job.",
    answer: "didn't get",
    options: [ "didn't get", "hadn't got","willn't got","didn't got" ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "When I arrived at the party, everybody .......................................... home.",
    answer: "had gone",
    options: [  "went", "has gone","had gone","go"  ]
  },
    {
    numb: 11,
    question: "I wondered who ........................................... the cat in.",
    answer: "had let",
    options: [  "let", "has let","had let","have let" ]
  },
    {
    numb: 12,
    question: " I thought I .......................................... the money.",
    answer: "had sent",
    options: [  "sent", "have sent","had sent","have sent" ]
  },
];